// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question:
      "Which of the following folk dance forms is associated with Gujarat?",
    answer: "Garba",
    options: ["Nautanki", "Garba", "Kathakali", "Bhagra"]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question:
      "Rabindranath Tagore's 'Jana Gana Mana' has been adopted as India's National Anthem. How many stanzas of the said song were adopted?",
    answer: "Only the first stanza",
    options: [
      "Only the first stanza",
      "The whole song",
      "Third and fourth stanza",
      "First and second stanza"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The National Song of India was composed by?",
    answer: "Bankim Chandra Chatterji",
    options: [
      "Rabindranath Tagore",
      "Iqbal",
      "Bankim Chandra Chatterji",
      "Jai Shankar Prasad"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question:
      "In which of the following festivals are boat races a special feature?",
    answer: "Onam",
    options: ["Pongal", "Bihu", "Navratri", "Onam"]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question:
      "Which of the following places is famous for Chikankari work, which is a traditional art of embroidery?",
    answer: "Lucknow",
    options: ["Jaipur", "Hyderabad", "Lucknow", "Mysore"]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "'Kathakali' is a folk dance prevalent in which state?",
    answer: "Kerala",
    options: ["Orissa", "Kerala", "Karnataka", "Manipur"]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "India's largest city by population?",
    answer: "Mumbai",
    options: ["Mumbai", "Kerala", "Chennai", "Delhi"]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Number of states and Union Territories in India?",
    answer: "28 states and 8 Union territories",
    options: [
      "29 states and 8 Union territories",
      "28 states and 7 Union territories",
      "28 states and 8 Union territories",
      "29 states and 8 Union territories"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Hindi Divas is celebrated in India on?",
    answer: "14th September",
    options: [
      "19th December",
      "14th September",
      "14th November",
      "15th January"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which is the largest coffee-producing state of India?",
    answer: "Karnataka",
    options: ["Orissa", "Kerala", "Karnataka", "Tamil Nadu"]
  }
];
